WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
They say that change is good for you,
that it keeps you on your toes.
Well, if that's true, I should be a fucking ballerina.
Who'd have believed that Babylon would be a bombed-out memory?
Or that Mel and Linz would be moving to Canada?
Or that Ted would at last find true love?
Or that - huh...
I can barely even say it, but i'll try.
That Mr. Brian Kinney would ask Mr. Justin Taylor
for his hand in marriage?
Holy shit!
Holy shit.
What?
You look...
Good?
Bad?
Laughable?
Beautiful.
I do?
It's not a question.
It's a declaration.
So try and be more emphatic
when the minister asks you if you want to go through with this.
I do.
Meanwhile, over at our house,
things were pretty much the same,
which, after nearly getting blown up,
was fine by me.
Okay, the difference between greek,
elizabethan and modern tragedy.
Uh, you're allowed one phone call.
Hush!
I'll get it.
Anything to avoid studying.
Hello?
How's he doing? Oh...
he's got a lot of catching up to do, but i'm hopeful.
Here, look at this. Hunter: Yeah, he's here.
Hold on for a second.
Uh, i mean, please hold on for a second.
Michael,
it's for you.
Huh.
Hello?
Yes, this is him... he.
Um, i'm sorry, um...
we're a little t thshor month.
Oh...
really?
Well, i... l-i'd be happy to.
You can count on it.
My pleasure.
Who is...
that was the committee for human rights.
Oh, i hope you told them weady gave.
I did, but they didn't want money.
Then what do they want?
Me.
So how's it going?
What? You have laryngitis?
Get your wisdom teeth extracted?
No, don't tell me. You've become a nun
and you've taken an oath of silence.
Yeah, i'm sister mary-go-fuckyourself.
You know, i haven't seen or heard from you in days,
except for an e-mail
cancelling your birthday dinner. Tad insisted
on whisking me off to mount flame for gay ski week,
just the two of us. Isn't that adorable?
Precious. Yeah, got to keep my thighs in shape,
and i don't mean just for the slopes.
Why did you do that?
How long have you known tad?
Three weeks. And you decided to cancel your plans
to be with your friends on your birthday
in order to be with him?
I need to dO Some pec-deck.
Those lycra ski suits are unforgiving.
Teddy. I don't want to talk about it.
You're just feeling jealous
because i've finally found the love of my life.
No, i am not jealous.
Nothing would make me happier
than for you to find the love of your life.
But to allow someone that you've known less than a month
to isolate you... he's not isolating me.
I want to be with him and i... i resent you
accusing him of... hi, sweetheart.
Hey, how's my baby? Very good.
Mmmmm...
i just passed sports chalet. They're having a sale.
We should check it out, for the trip.
Oh, hi, emmett.
Hello, tad.
"Your wife doesn't need to know...
neither does your girlfriend."
Our research indicates that the primary demo
for your new erectile dysfunction medication
is men between the ages of 45 and 75,
with a couple of gents in their 100s
expressing keen interest.
And there was also another group...
not to be overlooked:
"Your wife doesn't need to know
and neither does your boyfriend."
I find this crude, offensive and sophomoric.
Like "american pie" for seniors
than an ad offering hope for millions
suffering from a serious medical problem.
I have to say, i agree with ms. Dixon.
I want to see...
a happily married couple...
with flecks of grey in their hair,
embracing in front of a warm fire
with copy that reads: "rekindle the flame."
Not some dirty joke.
These are conservative times
the famous photograph
of immigrants arriving on ellis island.
They give you a new name
'cause they can't pronounce the one you've got.
"Peterson"?
You move into a one-room apartment,
start taking in laundry
and speaking english with a yiddish accent.
Hey, honey, it's toronto,
not the lower east side.
My cousin jeannie said there's a house for rent
down the street from her
with a starbucks and a gap on the corner.
Our future's secured.
Yours too.
Oh, it'll be strange not coming over,
seeing you and gus and jenny. I know.
You'll just have to come visit us.
You'll always have a place to stay.
If you ever decide to pack your bags and leave.
Mel. It was a joke.
I know you and brian will be happy.
We all will be.
The polls are showing
thince the bombing,
support for "stop prop 14" is up 28%.
The committee for human rights wants to take full advantage
of this sudden groundswell of sympathy
and turn i tinto a victory.
We want to show the general poputionla
that the gay community
is not just the transvestites and leather daddies
they see at the gay pride parade.
But for the most part, it's people like you,
like them, with a partner, a home, a family,
who were victims of this...
unspeakable act of violence.
But what do i have to do with it?
We want to introduce you at the press nference,
have you say a few words.
I... i'm not much of a public speaker.
I wouldn't know to whaty.
Not to worry.
We have some excellent speech writers
who'll be your voice.
Just give us your body.
Well, i haven't had a proposition that tempting in a long time.
So you'll do it?
I'm all yours.
What are those?
My revised ads for remson's instant wood.
What do you think? At that age,
i thought if they're on the floor,
it meant they've llen and they can't get up.
Which do you prefer?
None.
Just because you wouldn't watch geriatrics gonlde wi
doesn't mean they can't do it.
It's not funny, it's not sexy.
Haven't you heard?
Sex is out.
Who told you that?
Now put on your sluttiest club clothes
and bring plenty of drugs 'cause we're going out.
I wainkis th we'd spend a nice,
quiet evening at home.
Huh.
What the fuck's this?
It's the end of your life as you know it.
Your farewell appearance.
Kinney's last stand.
Welcome to that quaint,
heterosexual male tradition
known as "the stag party",
with a slightly gay twist.
Let's get this poor sucker a drink.
Come join us.
No.
You hurry back.
All right.
Hey, ringo. Tedster!
What'll it be? The usual?
Uh, make it one for my baby
and one for yours truly.
I see you hooked a hottie.
Yeah, he's a eper.
This time, it's for real.
On the house.
Ah, aren't you generous with the boss' money.
Anything for you. Thanks, ringo.
You're the best.
Hey, teddy.
Em.
I just want tO Say i'm sorry
for what i said about tad.
If you love him,
i'm sure he must be a wonderful person
because you're a wonderful person.
And if you want to know the truth,
ah... i am jealous.
But not because, uh, you have him.
Because he has you.
You still have me.
Cranberry and soda pour toi,
and cranberry and soda pour moi.
You can shove them both up your ass.
Tad.
Tad, would you stop?
What's wrong? What happened?
How could you do that?
Right in front of me,
like i was invisible.
Do what? You know perfectly well.
I really don't. You want a list?
How about coming on to that bartender?
Wh... ringo? I wasn't coming on to him.
I was telling him about you.
And he was congratulating me, he...
he gave us free drinks. Uh-huh.
And what about your beloved emmett?
I thought you told me that was over.
S ovit i. Emmett is a friend. That's all. , reohly?
Well, it looked like a lot more than that to me.
Well, whatever you think it looked like,
i was socializing. Nothing more.
You can call it whatever you want.
I call it being a slut!
Se me? You heard what i said.
Well, i'm not going to put up with that, okay?
I should never have gotten involved with you in the first place.
Why don't you go back to your friends?
I never want tO See you again.
Fuck you!
Can i have your attention, please?
I would like to offer a toast
in memory of brian kinney.
Outgoing, friendly, some say to a fault,
he never met a man he didn't like.
In his younger days,
brian dreamed of being a lawyer.
He said, "i want to get innocent men off...
I'll go to any length
to get to the bottom of things."
Later on in life,
he devoted himself to volunteer work.
Yes. It's true.
If he heard that someone was laid up,
or flat on his back,
he'd come time and time again
until they felt better.
So...
Now that he's gone,
i'm sure that there's not a man in this room
who wouldn't agree that he has left a hole
that can never be filled.
Here's to brian.
To brian!
Ah-ah...
Go for it, brian.
Oh, i just want to smack it.
No tan lines.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The prisoner respectfully chooses
not to partake of his last meal...
Aw-w.
But to be led instead to the gallows a hungry
but happy man.
Go on. Have a little fun.
It ain't so little.
No, seriously. You have my permission.
Hey, i'm content to take my winnings and go home.
You go for it, emmylou.
No...
Okay.
Come on, tiger.
Now remember,
when the bull-dyke minister says,
Ay i have the rings, please?"
That's when you bring the rings to daddy,
okay? Okay.
Now, let's practice.
You go stand over there.
Ready?
Yes.
May i have the rings, please?
Ha ha! Good boy.
You get a kiss for that.
Better late than never.
You finally grew a heart. Ss fhat.
You finally grew a heart.
Well, maybe you'll have the same luck
growing a penis.
Okay, big guy,
time for your nap.
No, we didn't play yet.
You'll see daddy later.
Uh-uh, buddy-boy.
I want you to know
that despite our past grievances... oh, christ,
can't you dykes just leave the country forever
without making a big deal out of it?
We'll try our best.
But before we do,
i want to wish you and justin
all the happiness on earth.
I mean that.
And i want you to know that i'm glad
you're going to be here for the wedding.
I mean that, too.
Why thank you, . Rian b
it would've really fucked up justin's seating arrangement.
It's justin's gift to us.
Going-away present.
I feel like gertrude stein.
You're not that heavy...
yet.
No, i mean it'ke having a picasso
before he becomes picasso.
He really is good, isn't he?
Better than good.
That's why you better be good to him.
Considering what he's sacrificing to be with you.
My son michael's press conference...
hamburger medium, fruit instead of fries...
tuesday at 2:30...
chicken caesar. Don't forget.
Dressing's on the side, honey.
What you studying?
The tudor monarchs.
I fucking loved english history.
Go ahead, ask me a question.
The wives of henry the eighth. In order.
Easy.
Catherine of aragon, anne boleyn,
jane seymour, anne of cleves,
kathryn howard...
who in the hell wae las th one?
Katherine parr!
Oh, wicked. Honey, if there's one thing i know about,
it's queens.
Deb, your order's up.
And if i hear one more fucking ding,
his head'sng goito roll faster than anne boleyn's.
Don't forget michael's press conference,
tuesday, 2:30.
That's when i've got my tranny support group.
So bring them along.
Then he accused me of coming on
to practically every guy at the stag party, including you.
Am i repeating myself?
I'm repeating myself,
just like my uncle louie.
He'd tell the same goddamn story over and over again,
like the time he peed next to bob hope.
Well, aunt lulah always said,
"a good story is worth retelling."
Ou go right ahead.
He became is ethirely different person.
A person l-i didn't even know.
He was so loving, and sweet,
and then he turned into this angry, suspicious...
...punitive,
paranoiac? Yeah, it's a classic case
of borderline personality disorder.
How could i have not seen it coming?
Because you didn't want to.
You wanted to be in love. Wh doesn't?
So stop beating yourself up.
Just be glad it's over.
Tied you tur o yo bed and fed you your dead parakeet.
Yeah, i suppose.
The right guy will come along, teddy.
You'll see.
Shake?
Right this way, gentlemen.
Oh, uh, i was planning on wearing this suit to the wedding
but with a different tie.
What do you think?
What, are you trying to upstage me?
I just want to look my best.
Doesn't matter to me if you're naked
as long as you're there to give me away.
Oh, well, in that case,
maybe i should wear my black leather pants.
At? You mean the ones you wore...
the first night we went to babylon.
They were so tight, you could barely move.
I know, my balls were killing me.
And that shirt you were wearing.
What was wrong with the shirt i was wearing?
No selfrespecting pimp would be caught dead in that.
Huh, i thought i looked pretty hot.
You did look pretty hot.
That night, l-i jerked off thin
well, what do you know?
That night, l-i jerked off thinking about you.
Well, what do you know?
I jerked off thinking about me too.
Who'd have thought that one day babylon would be gone
and we'd be sitting here in suits?
Talking about our wild and recklesslydressed youth.
Pathetic, huh?
Inevitable.
Gentlemen.
Merlot.
Uh, pepsi.
Uh... uh, make that a glass of white wine.
Almost ready. How are you doing?
He's scared shitless.
I'm fine, thank you.
Just stick to your speech
and i'm sure you'll do splendidly.
Um, excuse me.
Excuse me, honey.
Sorry, sweetheart, i think these are our seats.
My-my son's speaking.
Thank you.
My son's speaking.
Who are they?
His mother and her friends.
They can't sit there.
Move them to the back
out of camera range.
So, if you don't mind moving down...
there's a little more room in the back. Thanks.
Is something the matter?
Oh, just a little misunderstanding.
Those seats were adis sal the matter?
For who?
For couples with children like yourselves.
I apologize for the mix-up.
Good afternoon and welcome.
The committee for human rights
has called today's pres conference
in response to the unconscionable act of violence
that took the lives of seven
and critically injured dozens of others
at a recent benefit to stop proposition 14.
We express our sympathies to the families
who lost their loved ones,
and vow to continue fighting for equal rights
for all americans, straight and gay.
Now, i'd like you to meet one of the survivors
of that senseless tragedy, michael novotny.
Thank you, congresswoman.
"Thank you, congresswoman."
Oh... l-i already said that part.
few weeks ago
the doctors weren't sure i was going to make it.
But i was one of the lucky ones.
I'm here.
And as terrifying as that evening was,
i would be there again to defeat a bill
that would deny rights to americans
just because they're gay.
I have a loving partner and two wonderful kids,
a home, a small business.
The truth is, i'm just like you."
Actually, that's not the truth.
Sure, in a lot of ways i at the truth. You.'s
i want to be happy.
I want some security,
a little extra money in my pocket.
But in many ways, my life is nothing like yours.
Why should it be?
In the gay community, we have drag queenss
and leather daddies and trannies
and couples with children every colour of the rainbow.
My mother, who's standing way in the back
with some friends, my friends,
once told me that people are like snowflakes,
every one special and unique,
and in the morning you have to shovel them off the driveway.
But being different is what makes us all the same.
It's what makes us... family.
Yeah. -Here here!
Guess what? I called the lodge at mount flame
and got usan upgrade.
One of their deluxe suites on the club floor:
Fireplace, terrace, with a jacuzzi.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I mean after that little character assassination you performed on me,
i thought i'd never see you again.
Oh, let's just forget about that.
I don't want to forget about that.
I told you i had a few flaws, didn't i?
That's more than a flaw,
that's a serious malfunction.
Well, i just... sometimes i just get a little jealous, that's all.
That's all?
Yeah, but it's only because i love you.
And you love me. You know you do.
I loved the person i thought i knew.
I'm still the same person.
Well, i'm not.
Now, i want you to go.
I'm not going anywhere. Look,
i'm asking you to leave.
Ted, you'll get over this.
I already have.
So, if you don't mind,
i've had a really long day.
No, i'm not going anywhere.
You can't get rid of me.
Look, don't make me force you.
You let go. Then leave. Now!
I can't believe you're doing this.
I trusted you, i loved you.
I thought you were a good person.
I am a good person. No, you're shit!
Who the fuck do you think you are,
treating me like this?
No! No! I said i want you out.
I said i want you out. Ted!
Get the fuck out! Ted!
Ted!
Open the door.
Ted?
T... ted?
Ted, please, open the door.
Ted.
I had a dream last night
that we were in our new house.
Cooking?
Gardening?
Sitting in front of the fire?
Huh. Not exactly.
You were riding me in the stable,
diving into in the pool,
slamming me on the tennis court.
Well, that gives a new meaning to u.s. Open.
I better start practicing my serve.
Wouldn't you rather just cuddle?
What? I said wouldn't you rather just lie here and...
no. No, no, i heard what you said.
You said "cuddle".
So?
So, i have never, ever once
heard you even use that word,
much less actually want to do it.
Okay, so can we just rn t tu lights out? No! No.
Brian kinney fucks, sucks,
rims, rams but never... cuddles.
Okay, so i used a word that offends your sensibilities.
Oh... forgive me.
I apologize. I'll never
do it again. No. It's more than just th
every day we get closer to being married,
the person i know gets further away.
I'm right here.
But it's not you.
Looks like you, feels like you, but you...
you would never...
huh...
go to your own stag party
and not fuck every hot guy in sight.
You would never be more interested in gardening
than getting laid.
I'm just trying to make you happy.
I want you to do what makes you happy,
not me.
What about you?
Yes, you.
Not going to new york?
Fuck new york.
Conquering the art world?
Fuck the art world.
Why?
Because you're afraid? I'm not afraid.
Then what? I don't want it.
Bullshit. I don't.
It means nothing.
Would it still an nothing
if i wasn't here?
How do you expect me to give a you rational response
when the circumstances you've presented
are completely suppositional and, as such,
have no basis in reality?
Just answer the goddamn question. Aw, i don't know.
Well, i do.
I don't want to with someone
who sacrificed their life
and called it love...
to be with me.
Neither do i.
Ta-da!
What's that?
It's a quadruple bypass sundae.
Huh. Four kinds of ice cream,
what's that?
It's a quadruple bypass sundae.
Huh. Four kinds of ice cream,
four kinds of toppings, four kinds of sauce.
You want to give me a heart attack?
It's the only thing i could think of
that was sweeter than you.
Well,
i guess it beats getting hell was that for?
That's to remind you what'll happen to you
if you ever stop being the most loving son a mother has ever had.
Wouldn't you agree, ben?
Oh, i'd be scared not to.
Hey, kid.
Can you bring us some water?
Did you ever hear of "please"?
Sit down.
Well, what did i do now?
We got your report card.
Oh, shit.
You passed every subject
with "bs" and "cs".
No shit? That's awesome, dude.
That means you get to graduate with your class.
Next step, m.i.t.
That's theongahela institute of typing.
What's this?
It's a journal,
to write stuff in.
"H.n.b."
They're your initials,
if you'd like them to be.
Hunter novotny-bruckner.
Instead of being our foster son,
we'd like you to be our real son.
That is, if you'd like us to be your fathers.
You mean, you want to adopt me?
As soon as possible,
in case prop 14 passes.
So what do you say?
"Today,
michael and ben asked me
to be their son...
i said 'yes.'"
It's a rehearsal dinner but what's to rehearse?
They say, "i do," then they do it.
But what do you get the man who's had everyone?
A water buffalo.
Why the hell would brian want to fuck that?
It's to help cambodian farmers plough their fields
and provide milk for their children.
Well, that is so much more imaginative
than another boring old...
stngeir erlidren.
Well, that is so much more imaginative
than another boring old...
sterli silng place setting from tiffany's.
We would like to thank you all
for coming to our rehearsal dinner.
Howeveherer, t nothing to rehearse.
The wedding's off.
No, it's true.
We decided not to get married.
How the fuck do you return a water buffalo?
Based on our previous discussion,
i came up with a campaign that's more...
in line with your vision.
Cynthia.
Now we're cooking. Nice work, brian.
It's exactly what i had in mind.
Intimate, warm,
romantic.
All the feelings a woman associates with love-making.
Right, cynthia?
Uh, some women.
But there's only one problem.
Women aren't going to be buying a little pill
to make their dicks hard.
Men are.
Straight, gay,
democrat, republican, doesn't matter.
They're all paying 10 bucks a pop
for the same reason.
And trust me, ms. Dixon,
it's not to rekindle the flame.
They want to fuck.
They want tO Shoot their loads
as often as they can, as hard as they can,
all night long if tcan.
Not cuddle in
not cuddle in front of the fire
with some nice lady who looks like their mother.
Despite your personal feelings, we want the ad.
You can't have it.
Because,
despite these conservative times,
it's still all about sex.
So i suggest that you take your business elsewhere.
I made us a little something.
Thanks. I am famished.
I tagged all the pieces we're going to put in storage,
the ones we're selling
and the ones we're giving away.
I don't suppose there's any point
in keeping this old table.
Christ, you're such a shikseh.
Why don't you just say it?
You want the table. I don't.
I just thought it's a shame to...
All right. I want the table. Good.
We'll keep it.
I keep telling myself it's just a house.
A bunch of notvery-grand or even spacious rooms,
but everywhere i look, i see us.
Hmmm. Like over there,
at gus'bris.
Two, in the kitchen,
now!
You mean, his almostbris.
Or the front gate
where i proposed to you.
Or the time i was sitting there and...
you told me...
i'll stay until after the baby's born.
What?
Nothing.
Just a bad memory.
They're part of us too.
Without them...
how do we appreciate the good ones?
What do you say...
we make one more memory?
Mmm.
The glories of nature.
The "beautiful for spacious skies",
the "purple mountain's majesty".
Huh. Don't forget the "fruited plains".
Aren't you glad you came? Mmm.
Thrilled.
Would have lost the room deposit if we hadn't.
Well, honey, i know it's not exactly
the romantic getaway you'd hoped for, but, um...
i promise you, you're going to have a fabulous birthday anyway.
God. Oh, god.
Talk about your fire hazard.
Thatng's thiore flaming than you.
Geez. It's 40 candles.
One for every year, plus one to grow on.
Oh, do you have to remind me?
Well, it's quite an achievement to get to be your age.
You know wh i mat
well, hurry up and make a wish
before the place burns down.
Huh. You know...
every year, i always wish for the same thing:
A boyfriend.
Someone to love, who'll love me.
This year i think i'm going to wish for something else.
The wisdom and the maturity to realize that...
i won't find what i want by looking for it.
Not expect someone else to give me what i never gave myself.
That i'm not a half waiting to be made a whole.
And even if that special person never comes along...
i'll be just fine.
Ted?
Blake?
I thought it was you.
Oh... what are you doing here?
I'm on the gay ski team now.
And it's gay ski week.
Right. Huh!
Ah... uh, you remember... emmett.
Yeah, wow. Uh, what a surprise.
And teddy was just about to hang up his skis.
Huh! You ski?
I'm lucky if i can walk. No, we're...
we're here for my birthday.
Uh, strictly as friends.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
And y... you, uh... uh...
no.
Oh.
I'm with, uh, 11 other men.
well, you know, i...
i always preferred the...
fulfilling.
Well, i'll, uh...
catch you later.
Uh, no, hey. Hey...
why not now?
Yummy cake to myself. His
thanks, em.
Pardon me,
but aren't you emmett honeycutt
of the hazelhurst, mississippi honeycutts?
Why, yes i am.
And, uh, you are...?
Ah...
oh my god.
You're calvin culpe
pp and, uh, you are...?
Ah...
oh my god.
You're calvin culpeer. Pp
You were on the boys' swim team in high school.
I used to go to those meets
just hoping your trunks would slip off.
Oh, now...
So did i.
Hmm...
so, uh, what do you say
we go back to my room and, uh...
reminiscout old times?
There's not that mto reminisce about.
I know.
I love you, honey bun.
I hope eve ry-dy peed.
Whenever i used to take michael anywhere,
no sooner we'd leave the house than he'd say,
"ma, i gotta tinkle."
And i'd say, "why?
You couldn't have done it before you left the house?"
Do you mind if we not relive the golden days of yesteryear?
And i'd say, "why? So to speak. Ughter
you couldn't have done it before you left the house?"
Do you mind if we not relive the golden days of yesteryear?
Tires, the water, the oil, the brakes. Cked the
never send a fag to do a dyke's work.
And remember to call
when you arrive. Well, how can we forget
when michael will be calling us every five minutes to remind us?
Well, i guess it's time we... hold it.
I don't care where you're going
and i don't care what you're doing,
but you better get your asses back here
every thanksgiving, christmas, 4th of july,
chanukahand mother's day.
'Cause you know how i feel about family.
Well, we wouldn't be one without you, deb.
Huh!
Take good care of my granddaughter.
Mmmm... oh!
I love you.
Ready to roll.
Mel. Brian.
Don't you think i'm not coming utherp
for my granddaughter's birthday,
so you better make room.
You'll be all right?
Without you cwazy wesbians?
I meant justin.
He's a selfish prick,
thinks only of himself.
You taught him well.
I know.
I'm sorry.
No apologies.
No regrets.
Are we leaving some time today?
Goodbye, son.
Bye-bye, sweetheart.
Drive carefully.
Call us when you get there.
We miss you already.
Bye. Have fun.
See you soon.
We love you.
Bye-bye. Bye.
When's your flight?
10:00.
I think i've finally found a place to stay.
Daphne has a friend in the east village.
Finding a work space is going to be difficult.
Apparently, everything costs a fortune.
Well, you'll manage. You always do.
I'll be back.
And you'll come there.
We're going to see each other all the time.
You don't know that.
Neither do i.
Whether we see each other next weekend
or next month...
never again...
it doesn't matter. It's only time.
Mmmm.
You didn't return them?
I didn't return them.
We don't need rings or vows
to prove that we love each other.
We already know that.
You did it.
Did what?
Became...
the best homosexual you could possibly be.
Thought you might like some company.
Why are you out so late?
It's barely midnight.
The good old days, we'd just be heading off to babylon.
Babylon'gones
so are the good old days.
Not yet.
Christ.
What did you expect?
Dancing boys?
Glitter falling from on high?
This is where we came
the night of our senior prom
when we dumped our dates.
Hmm, the ghastly judy zumholtz.
And the equally dreadful carol kolodny.
We snuck in. We got stoned.
Danced with our shirts off.
You got blown in the back room.
This is where it all began.
And ended.
But it's who we are.
It's what made us.
Didn't you say that...
that's all a cheap illusion,
and that outside, life goes on
but in here, nothing ever changes?
I did say that. Yes.
But that was before i understood...
that some things aren't meant to change.
Dance with me.
Why not?
Well, for one thing, there's no music.
Of course there is. Can't you hear it?
The old "thumpa-thumpa"?
Oh, watch it, asshole.
You want to bust your stitches?
I'm fine.
Come on.
Come on!
Shake that groove thing.
You shake it, mikey.
I am too... what? Old?
You'll always be young.
You'll always be beautiful.
You're brian kinney, for fuck's sake.
So what
our song.
So the thumpathumpa continues.
It always will, no matter what happens,
no matter who's president.
As our lady of disco, the divine miss gloria gaynor,
has always sung to us:
"We will survive."